Guide to the Jacques E. Levy Research Collection on Cesar Chavez
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Principal Cesar Chavez Tape Collection, 1969-1976; Series I; 3.99; (14 boxes)
  - AUDIOTAPES
    - Principal Audiotapes
      - Tape 61. Salinas march and rally, press conference, JEL notes, Cesar Chavez and Fred Ross, Cesar Chavez announces fast, 1970 August 2-11; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002099366693)
        Transcript: Volume 2 CC: 887-903, stored in: box 2, folder 149
      - Tape 62. Cesar Chavez speech, Spanish transcript, press conference, JEL notes, Sunday strike vote in Salinas, 1970 August 12; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002099366701)
        Transcript: Volume 2 CC: 903-928, File 30, stored in: box 6, folder 203 and box 6, folder 203
      - Tape 62 (#2). Dr. Jerome Lackner re: fast condition, 1970 August 14; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002099366719)
        Transcript: Volume 3 CC: 1146, stored in: box 2, folder 156. This audiotape was not reformatted to a CD. Dr. Lackner's comments on Cesar Chavez's health after a 4-day fast runs for 2:40 minutes
      - Tape 63. UFWOC strategy session with Marshall Ganz, Dolores Huerta, Fred Ross, Jerry Cohen; Cesar Chavez speech; Cesar Chavez and Bill Kircher; Marshall Ganz, Dolores Huerta; Bill Kircher press conference, Mayor of Salinas, 1970 August 18-September 5; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002099366727)
        Transcript: Volume 2 CC: 928-976, stored in: box 2, folders 151-152
      - Tape 64. Bill Kircher press conference and Mayor of Salinas, Bill Kircher on street, 1970 September 5; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002099366735)
        Transcript: Volume 2 CC: 977-980, stored in: box 2, folder 152
      - Tape 65. Rally outside Salinas union headquarters with Cesar Chavez; Jerry Cohen; Cesar Chavez and Jerry Cohen; Helen Manning; Cesar Chavez press conference; Jack Armstrong; press conference with Freeland of the Council of CA Growers; Tom Driscoll, Cesar Chavez, Dolores Huerta, Marshall Ganz, Jerry Cohen; JEL notes, Rally with Cesar Chavez and Jerry Cohen, King City labor camp incident, 1970 September 9-12; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002099366743)
        Transcript: Volume 2 CC: 980-1014, stored in box 2, folder 152, and box 3, folder 153
      - Tape 66. Cesar Chavez speech, Fred Ross and Marshall Ganz, Cesar Chavez, Press conference, Herb Fleming, Mass, 1970 September 14-17; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002099366750)
        Transcript: Volume 3 CC: 1014-1051, stored in box 3, folders 153-154
      - Tape 67. Rally with Cesar Chavez, Jack Henning, Marshall Ganz; Press conference; JEL notes; Boycotters meeting with Cesar Chavez, Marshall Ganz, Dolores Huerta, Manuel Chavez at seaside, 1970 September 23-24; 1 (Box 57, Item barcode 39002099366768)
        Transcript: Volume 3 CC: 1052-1077, stored in: box 3, folder 154
      - Tape 68. Boycotters meeting with Cesar Chavez, Marshall Ganz, Dolores Huerta, Manuel Chavez continued, 1970 September 24; 1 (Box 57, Item barcode 39002099366776)
        Transcript: Volume 3 CC: 1078-1113, stored in: box 3, folders 154-155
      - Tape 69. Jerry Cohen press conference, Jerry Cohen interview, Thorne Gray, Cesar Chavez, 1971 January 28-29; 1 (Box 57, Item barcode 39002099366784)
        Transcript: Volume 3 CC: 1272-1321, stored in: box 3, folder 159
      - Tape 69 (#2). Cesar Chavez on Merv Griffin Show, 1971 February 2; 1 (Box 57, Item barcode 39002099366792)
        Transcript: Volume 3 CC: 1322-1327, stored in: box 3, folder 159
      - Tape 70. Lionel Steinberg, president, David Freedman, 1971 June 11; 1 (Box 57, Item barcode 39002099366800)
        Transcript: File 26 LS: 1-67, Volume 3 CC: 1268-1271, stored in: box 6, folders 198-199 and box 3, folder 160
      - Tape 71. Lionel Steinberg concluded, 1971 June 11; 1 (Box 57, Item barcode 39002099366818)
      - Tape 72. Larry Shears with Jerry Cohen and Richard Chavez, 1971 December 17; 1 (Box 57, Item barcode 39002099366826)
        Transcript: Assassination Plot Collection File 38: pp. 5-46, stored in: box 47, folder 913
      - Tape 73. Larry Shears with Jerry Cohen and Richard Chavez in Bakersfield, 1971 December 22; 1 (Box 57, Item barcode 39002099366834)
        Transcript: Assassination Plot Collection File 38: pp. 47-91, stored in: box 47, folder 913
      - Tape 74. Larry Shears on Channel 23, Larry Shears with Jerry Cohen and Richard Chavez, 1971 Dec 17-22; 1 (Box 57, Item barcode 39002099366842)
        Transcript: Assassination Plot Collection File 38: pp. 1-4, 92-113, stored in: box 48, folders 913-195
      - Tape 75. Larry Shears press conference at home of Paul Schrade's, 1971 December 23; 1 (Box 57, Item barcode 39002099366859)
        Transcript: Assassination Plot Collection File 38: pp. 114-161, stored in: box 47, folders 913-195
      - Tape 76. Cesar Chavez, 1971 October 30; 1 (Box 57, Item barcode 39002099366867)
        Transcript: Volume 3 CC: 1261-1267, stored in: box 3, folder 159
      - Tape 77. Cesar Chavez, 1972 November 9; 1 (Box 57, Item barcode 39002099366875)
        Transcript: Volume 3 CC: 1203-1260, stored in: box 3, folders 157-158
      - Tape 78. Cesar Chavez from Santa Maria to Coachella to Phoenix, 1973 January 8-9; 1 (Box 57, Item barcode 39002099366883)
        Transcript: Volume 3 CC: 1261-1303 (second set of pages with these numbers), stored in: box 3, folder 160
      - Tape 79. Cesar Chavez in Phoenix, JEL notes, 1973 January 10-11; 1 (Box 57, Item barcode 39002099366891)
        Transcript: Volume 3 CC: 1304-1348 (1304-1325 is a second set of pages with these numbers), stored in: box 3, folders 160-161
      - Tape 79 (#2). Cesar Chavez, 1973 January 10-11; 1 (Box 57, Item barcode 39002099366909)
      - Tape 80. Cesar Chavez, La Paz to Yuma to Phoenix to La Paz, 1973 March 10-11; 1 (Box 57, Item barcode 39002099366917)
        Transcript: Volume 3 CC: 1349-1380, stored in: box 3, folder 161
      - Tape 81. Cesar Chavez report to boycotters after AFL-CIO visit in Coachella, in Spanish, boycott report in San Jose, 1973 June 10; 1 (Box 57, Item barcode 39002099366925)
      - Tape 82. Cesar Chavez from San Jose to Keene and Cesar Chavez report to staff, 1973 June 11; 1 (Box 58, Item barcode 39002099366933)
        Transcript: Volume 3 CC: 1381-1438, stored in: box 3, folder 162
      - Tape 83. End of Keene report, 1973 June 11; 1 (Box 58, Item barcode 39002099366941)
      - Tape 84. Phone call to Julian Bach, Cesar Chavez speech, Cesar Chavez from La Paz to Santa Maria, 1973 June 25-July 8; 1 (Box 58, Item barcode 39002099366958)
        Transcript: Volume 3 & 4 CC: 1439- 1480 stored in: Box 3, folder 162 and box 4, folder 163
      - Tape 85. Cesar Chavez continued, La Paz and Livingston, 1973 July 8-10; 1 (Box 58, Item barcode 39002099366966)
        Transcript: Volume 4 CC: 1480-1506, stored in: box 4, folder 163
      - Tape 86. Cesar Chavez continued from Modesto to San Francisco, Msgr. George Higgins in Bakersfield, 1973 July 10-14; 1 (Box 58, Item barcode 39002099366974)
        Transcript: Volume 4 CC: 1506-1550, stored in: box 4, folder 163
      - Tape 87. Msgr. George Higgins continued, Cesar Chavez to picket line (Spanish), 1973 July 14-August 3; 1 (Box 58, Item barcode 39002099366982)
        Transcript: Volume 4 CC: 1551-1569, stored in: box 4, folder 164
      - Tape 88. Cesar Chavez at La Paz, JEL notes, Cesar Chavez, boycott staff start, 1973 November 13-15; 1 (Box 58, Item barcode 39002099366990)
        Transcript: Volume 4 CC: 1570-1620, stored in: box 4, folder 164
      - Tape 89. Cesar Chavez concluded at La Paz, JEL notes, Jerry Cohen, 1973 November 15-December 18; 1 (Box 58, Item barcode 39002099367006)
        Transcript: Volume 4 CC: 1620-1654, stored in: box 4, folders 164-165
      - Tape 90. Jerry Cohen concluded at La Paz, Mack Lyons, Cesar Chavez, 1973 December 18-1974 January 12; 1 (Box 58, Item barcode 39002099367014)
        Transcript: Volume 4 CC: 1654-1696, stored in: box 4, folder 165
      - Tape 91. Cesar Chavez on way to San Diego, back to La Paz, 1974 January 11-February 4; 1 (Box 58, Item barcode 39002099367022)
        Transcript: Volume 4 CC: 1697-1784, stored in: box 4, folders 165-166
      - Tape 92. Cesar Chavez continued from Keene to L.A., 1974 February 4; 1 (Box 58, Item barcode 39002099367030)
      - Tape 93. Press conference for Art Torres and Cesar Chavez, Cesar Chavez, Richard Ybarra, 1974 February 4-5; 1 (Box 58, Item barcode 39002099367048)
        Transcript: Volume 4 CC: 1785-1829, stored in: box 4, folder 167
      - Tape 94. Cesar Chavez at La Paz concluded, 1974 February 5-March 16; 1 (Box 58, Item barcode 39002099367055)
        Transcript: Volume 4 CC: 1830-1840, 1856-1875, stored in: box 4, folders 167 and 168
      - Tape 95. Cesar Chavez, Cesar Chavez with boycotters, 1974 March16-17; 1 (Box 58, Item barcode 39002099367063)
        Transcript: Volume 4 CC: 1876-1917A, stored in: box 4, folders 168-169
      - Tape 96. Cesar Chavez with boycotters in Berkeley continued, 1974 March 17; 1 (Box 58, Item barcode 39002099367071)
        Transcript: Volume 4 & 5 CC: 1903-1943, stored in: box 4, folder 169
      - Tape 97. Cesar Chavez with boycotters in Berkeley concluded, Cesar Chavez, 1974 March 17; 1 (Box 58, Item barcode 39002099367089)
        Transcript: Volume 5 CC: 1944-1996, stored in: box 4, folder 170
      - Tape 98. Cesar Chavez, San Francisco to Keene, 1974 March 18; 1 (Box 58, Item barcode 39002099367097)
        Transcript: Volume 5 CC: 1997-2042, stored in: box 4, folders 170-171
      - Tape 99. Cesar Chavez San Francisco to Keene concluded, Jerry Cohen, JEL notes and Cesar Chavez, 1974 March 18-19; 1 (Box 59, Item barcode 39002099367105)
        Transcripts: Volume 5 CC: 2043-2086, File 31, stored in: box 4, folder 171 and box 6, folder 204
      - Tape 100. Cesar Chavez speech, questions and answers after speech in San Francisco, 1974 March 18; 1 (Box 59, Item barcode 39002099367113)
        Transcript: Volume 4 CC: 1841-1855, stored in: box 4, folder 168
      - Tape 101. Eliseo Medina in Keene, Anna Puharich at La Paz, 1974 March 28-30; 1 (Box 59, Item barcode 39002099367121)
        Transcripts: File 17 EM: 1-24, File 22 AP: 1-21, stored in: box 5, folder 189 and box 6, folder 194
      - Tape 102. Cesar Chavez continued, Cesar Chavez, 1974 May 23-24; 1 (Box 59, Item barcode 39002099367139)
        Transcript: Volume 5 CC: 2087-2132, stored in: box 4, folder 172
      - Tape 103. Cesar Chavez continued, Manuel Chavez at La Paz, 1974 May 24; 1 (Box 59, Item barcode 39002099367147)
        Transcript: Volume 5 CC: 2133-2177, stored in: box 4, folders 172-173
      - Tape 104. Marshall Ganz in Keene, Richard Chavez, Helen Chavez in San Jose, 1974 June 16; 1 (Box 59, Item barcode 39002099367154)
        Transcript: Volume 5 CC: 2188-2229, stored in: box 4, folder 173
      - Tape 105. "Helen Chavez continued, Richard Chavez" [later taped over, is now a Jacques Levy talk on French tapestry maker Jean Lurçat], 1974 June 16, undated; 1 (Box 59, Item barcode 39002099367162)
        Transcript: Volume 5 CC: 2230-2251, stored in: box 4, folder 173. Identified as Helen Chavez and Richard Chavez interview, but upon reformatting, the tape was discovered to be of a talk by Jacques Levy on French tapestry maker Jean Lurçat. The transcript is of Helen and Richard Chavez
    - Additional Tapes
      Audiovisual material. Restricted fragile. Reference copies can be found in boxes 85-86. Consult Access Services for further information.
      - Miscellaneous
        - Tape 106. Cesar Chavez talking about Teamsters etc., JEL Questions Cesar Chavez, JEL manuscript, undated; 1 (Box 59, Item barcode 39002099367170)
        - Tape 107. Cesar Chavez speech in Santa Rosa, 1972 September 28; 1 (Box 59, Item barcode 39002099367188)
      - Europe Trip
        - Tape 108. Cesar Chavez BBC interview in London, Covent Garden interviews, press conference, BBC radio interview, Thames TV interview with Jack Jones of TGWU, 1974 September 16-17; 1 (Box 59, Item barcode 39002099367196)
        - Tape 109. Cesar Chavez Norway speech, press interviews, Swedish TV interview, Swedish press conference, 1974 September 20-24; 1 (Box 59, Item barcode 39002099367204)
        - Tape 110. Cesar Chavez Assisi, Italy talk with Bishop Donnelly & Msgr. Higgins; World Council of Churches interview with Michael de Vries, Francis Smith, Andre Goy; talk in Bonn, West Germany, 1974 September 27-October 1; 1 (Box 59, Item barcode 39002099367212)
        - Tape 111. Cesar Chavez Bonn, West Germany talk continued, Copenhagen press conference, [Brussels press conference?], 1974 October 1-5; 1 (Box 59, Item barcode 39002099367220)
          No transcript. Brussels press conference described as being present on audiotape is not there
        - Tape 112. Cesar Chavez report on European trip on plane, 1974 October 9; 1 (Box 59, Item barcode 39002099367238)
        - Tape 113. Cesar Chavez Paris-NY plane interview for book, talks about meeting Pope, 1974 October 9; 1 (Box 59, Item barcode 39002099367246)
      - Post Book Interviews
        - Tape 114. Cesar Chavez at La Paz, JEL interview, 1976 January 3; 1 (Box 59, Item barcode 39002099367253)
        - Tape 115. Cesar Chavez at Democratic Convention in New York, 1976 July 14; 1 (Box 59, Item barcode 39002099367261)
        - Tape 116. JEL notes on Giumarra negotiations, sides 1 and 2, 1970 July 21; 1 (Box 60, Item barcode 39002099367279)
          Transcript: JEL Written Notes File 1 pp. 16-82, stored in: box 41, folder 783
        - Tape 117. JEL notes on Giumarra negotiations, sides 3 and 4, 1970 July 21; 1 (Box 60, Item barcode 39002099367287)
        - Tape 118. JEL notes, Giumarra notes concluded, side 5, 1970 July 21 (Box 70, Item barcode 39002099367295)
        - Tape 119. JEL notes on Shears, assassination plot, 1972 February; 1 (Box 60, Item barcode 39002099367303)
        - Tape 120. JEL notes, 1973 July 18-August 4; 1 (Box 60, Item barcode 39002099367311)
        - Tape 121. JEL notes, 1973 August 4-September 1; 1 (Box 60, Item barcode 39002099367329)
        - Tape 122. UFW convention, Senator Kennedy speech, JEL notes and "so-called democracy", memorial mass with Joan Baez, 1973 September 23; 1 (Box 60, Item barcode 39002099367337)
          Transcript: File 32, stored in: box 6, folder 205
        - Tape 123. JEL notes on T, UFW, AFL talks in Washington, D. C., 1973 September 26; 1 (Box 60, Item barcode 39002099367345)
        - Tape 124. JEL notes, undated; 1 (Box 60, Item barcode 39002099367352)
  - TRANSCRIPTS
    - Cesar Chavez Transcripts
      - Index to first five volumes (Box 1, Folder 129-131)
      - Vol. 1, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 132-140)
      - Vol. 2, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 141-152)
        Pages 629-631 do not exist. Includes first draft of typescript for pages 928-956. Includes as part of transcript Levy's written notes on the negotiations with large scale growers in June 1970
      - Vol. 3, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 153-162)
        Includes a second numbering of pages 1251-1325 for tapes 78-79. Pages 1328-1329 do not exist. Includes two pages of holograph notes
      - Vol. 4, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 163-169)
        Includes pages numbered 1903A-1917A, and four pages of an unidentified transcript
      - Vol. 5, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 170-174)
        Includes a transcript of an interview with Al Rojas, not described in Levy's list of audiotapes and transcripts
    - Other Transcripts
      - Index to selected other transcripts (Box 4, Folder 175)
      - File 6. Richard Chavez, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 176)
      - File 7. Reverend James "Jim" Drake (Box 5, Folder 177)
      - File 8. Elaine Elinson, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 178)
      - File 9. Paul Espinoza, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 179)
      - File 10. Family Gathering (Chavez), n.d. (Box 5, Folder 180-182)
        Accompanied by miscellaneous related transcript notes
      - File 11. Dolores Huerta, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 183-184)
        Accompanied by holograph notes on Huerta
      - File 12. Larry Itliong, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 185)
      - File 13. Michael Klein, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 186)
      - File 15. Jon Lewis, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 187)
      - File 16. Philip Mason, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 188)
      - File 17. Eliseo Medina, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 189)
      - File 18. Rita Medina, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 190)
      - File 19. Gilbert Padilla, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 191)
      - File 20. Philippine Labor Attaché, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 192)
      - File 21. Playboy, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 193)
      - File 22. Anna Puharich, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 194)
      - File 23. Hijnio Rangel, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 195)
      - File 24. Fred Ross, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 196)
        Includes as part of transcript Levy's written notes on Fred Ross
      - File 25. Scenic Notes - Gila Valley to San Jose, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 197)
      - File 26. Lionel Steinberg, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 198-199)
      - File 27. Transcript Tape 2A, March to Sacramento 1966, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 200)
      - File 28. Transcript Correction Tape 62A, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 201)
      - File 29. Transcript of Tape 45B, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 202)
      - File 30. Transcript of Spanish Tape 62A, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 203)
      - File 31. Depositions: D. Steele & William Grami (Tape 99B), n.d. (Box 6, Folder 204)
      - File 32. JEL notes: CC, "This so-called democracy" (Tape 122B), n.d. (Box 6, Folder 205)
      - File 33. Chavez note approving of JEL book, 10/8/74. Photocopy, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 206)
      - File 34. Pope Paul VI transcript. Photocopy, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 207)
- Miscellaneous Cesar Chavez Tape Collection, 1969-1976; Series II; 0.67; (5 boxes)
  Series II, Miscellaneous Cesar Chavez Tape Collection, is organized into two subseries: Audiotapes and Transcripts, and contains a wide variety of material taped by Levy. Transcripts exist where noted. The audiotapes are restricted; reference copies on CD-ROM have been made.
  Boxes 61-64 contain audiovisual material. Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Contact Access Services for further information.
  - AUDIOTAPES
    Audiovisual material. Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Contact Access Services for further information.
    - Tape 1. Nixon press conference, 1970 May 8; 1 (Box 61, Item barcode 39002099368053)
    - Tape 2. Cesar Chavez and Daryl Arnold on "Today Show", 1970 December 1 (Box 61, Item barcode 39002099368061)
      Daryl Arnold was president of the Free Marketing Council from 1970-71.
    - Tape 3. Helen Chavez, JEL notes, 1970 December 5; 1 (Box 61, Item barcode 39002099368079)
      Transcript: File 1: Chavez in Jail, p. 1, stored in: box 7, folder 256
    - Tape 4. Ethel Kennedy visit with Cesar Chavez, Jerry Cohen, JEL notes, 1970 December 6; 1 (Box 61, Item barcode 39002099368087)
      Transcript: File 2: Ethel Kennedy in Salinas, pp. 1-6, stored in: box 7, folder 257
    - Tape 5. Mrs. Martin Luther King, Jr. at rally in Salinas, 1970; 1 (Box 61, Item barcode 39002099368095)
    - Tape 6. Anti-UFW rally, Salinas Valley, 1970; 1 (Box 61, Item barcode 39002099368103)
    - Tape 7. Calexico rally, Calexico press conference, Reverend Jesse Jackson and Roberta Plank, Cesar Chavez, 1970 January 10; 1 (Box 61, Item barcode 39002099368111)
      Transcript: File 3: Chavez re book's style, pp. 1-8, stored in box 7, folder 258
    - Tape 8. Napa, 1971 August 8; 1 (Box 61, Item barcode 39002099368129)
    - Tape 9. Rally in Salinas with Cesar Chavez, 1971 August 28; 1 (Box 61, Item barcode 39002099368137)
    - Tape 10. Clinic dedication in Delano, Cesar Chavez in St. Helena and press conference, 1971 September 12-October 16; 1 (Box 61, Item barcode 39002099368145)
    - Tape 11. Cesar Chavez press conference after AFL-T agreement, 1971; 1 (Box 61, Item barcode 39002099368152)
    - Tape 12. A. E. Stevenson, Jr. hearing, 1972 January 11; 1 (Box 61, Item barcode 39002099368160)
    - Tape 13. Larry Shears, Horning, Jerry Cohen, 1972 May 23-26; 1 (Box 61, Item barcode 39002099368178)
    - Tape 14. Cesar Chavez fast and Joan Baez at mass in Phoenix, 1972 June 4; 1 (Box 61, Item barcode 39002099368186)
    - Tape 15. Cesar Chavez at worker meeting in Santa Maria (Spanish), 1973 January 8; 1 (Box 61, Item barcode 39002099368194)
    - Tape 16. Earle Caldwell interviews Cesar Chavez, 1973 July 18; 1 (Box 61, Item barcode 39002099368202)
    - Tape 17. JEL helps Cesar Chavez prepare for UFW Convention, 1973 September 21; 1 (Box 61, Item barcode 39002099368210)
    - Tape 18. UFW Convention speeches, JEL notes, Paul Hall speech, 1973 September 21-23; 1 (Box 62, Item barcode 39002099368228)
    - Tape 19. JEL interviewed on KBBF, Santa Rosa, 1973 October 9; 1 (Box 62, Item barcode 39002099368236)
    - Tape 20. Anti-UFW press conference, Coachella, 1973; 1 (Box 62, Item barcode 39002099368244)
    - Tape 21. Fred Ross at home in Corte Madera, 1974 November 7; 1 (Box 62, Item barcode 39002099368251)
    - Tape 22. Bill Soltero, and other interviews, with publisher, Arizona, 1975 March 17; 1 (Box 62, Item barcode 390020993682699)
    - Tape 23. Governor Jerry Brown on "Firing Line", 1975 October 18; 1 (Box 62, Item barcode 39002099368277)
    - Tape 24. JEL interviewed on KBBF, KFRC, KOVR, KPIX, 1975 October 29-1976 November 6; 1 (Box 62, Item barcode 39002099368285)
    - Tape 25. "Inside an Enigma" with Leo Lee, NPR broadcast on KQED-FM about Jerry Brown, 1975 November 26; 1 (Box 62, Item barcode 39002099368293)
    - Tape 26. Jerry Cohen, Mark Grossman reporting to JEL, 1975; 1 (Box 62, Item barcode 39002099368301)
    - Tape 27. Bill Folks radio show "Open Line" interview with JEL, 1976 January; 1 (Box 62, Item barcode 39002099368319)
    - Tape 28. JEL interviewed on KNX-FM, KFRE, KJEO-TV, KVEN, 1976 January 7-February 2; 1 (Box 62, Item barcode 39002099368327)
    - Tape 29. JEL interviewed on KTRB, Modesto (1 of 2 audiocassettes), 1976 February 12; 1 (Box 62, Item barcode 39002099368335)
    - Tape 30: JEL interviewed on KTRB about book, Modesto (2 of 2 audiocassettes), 1976 February 12; 1 (Box 62, Item barcode 39002099368343)
    - Tape 31. JEL interviewed by Jim Dunbar on KGO in San Francisco, 1976 March 23; 1 (Box 62, Item barcode 39002099368350)
    - Tape 32. JEL interviewed on KFOG in San Francisco, Cesar Chavez on "In Depth" on KCBS, 1974 April 11; 1 (Box 62, Item barcode 39002099368368)
    - Tape 33. John Maher and Jimmy Carter at UFW Convention, Fresno, 1976 September 5; 1 (Box 62, Item barcode 39002099368376)
    - Tape 34. Mexican music [union songs?], 1976; 1 (Box 62, Item barcode 39002099368384)
    - Tape 35. Miscellaneous Cesar Chavez, undated; 1 (Box 63, Item barcode 39002099368392)
    - Tape 36. Excerpts of interviews with Cesar Chavez, possibly Cesar Chavez family interview recollection of early years, 1969-75; 1 (Box 63, Item barcode 39002099368400)
    - Tape 37. Brief Press Conference, undated; 1 (Box 63, Item barcode 39002099368418)
    - Tape 38. Grower Press Conference, undated; 1 (Box 63, Item barcode 39002099368426)
    - Tape 39. Panel discussing agribusiness in California including JEL, possibly El Camino College, undated; 1 (Box 63, Item barcode 39002099368434)
    - Tape 40. Southwest Labor Conference @ UCSC, undated; 1 (Box 63, Item barcode 39002099368442)
    - Tape 41. Cesar Chavez speaking in Spanish (1 of 2 audiocassettes), undated; 1 (Box 63, Item barcode 39002099368459)
    - Tape 41. Cesear Chavez speaking in Spanish, undated; 1 (Box 63)
      This audiocassette appears to be a duplicate.
    - Tape 42. Cesar Chavez in Spanish (2 of 2 audiocassettes), undated; 1 (Box 63, Item barcode 39002099368467)
    - Tape 43. Person translating Spanish text for JEL, undated; 1 (Box 63, Item barcode 39002099368475)
    - Tape 44. "Day without Sunshine," a documentary, undated; 1 (Box 63, Item barcode 39002099368483)
    - Tape 45. JEL interviewed on KLOK, December 8; 1 (Box 63, Item barcode 39002099368491)